<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tourism</string>
    <string name="y_des"> <b>Yamunotri </b>Temple lies in the western Garhwal Himalayas at an elevation of about 3,291mts.The majestic mountains, mesmerizing springs of Surya Kund and Gouri Kund  flowing hot and cold water respectively,and River Yamuna flowing gracefully provides a tranquil-filled atmosphere around Yamunotri temple.People believes that on “Akshaya Tritiya” ,the goddess comes back to grace Yamunotri again. So, that the both closing and opening ceremonies of the Yamunotri shrine are brought about with celebrations .
 </string>
    <string name="KHARSALIDES">• <b>Kharsali </b>is a quaint Himalayan village which is about 8km from Yamunotri.There is an Untouched village of Kharsali also known as “KHUSHIMATH” which is cradled with love in the Uttarkashi district of Uttarkhand.We can walk around and explore the village at our steps.Since the Yamunotri Shrine becomes inaccessible in winters ,due to heavy snowfall.So,that the deity is brought here for worshipping.
    </string>
    <string name="hanu">
        •	<b>Hanuman Chatti </b> is located at the confluence of the Hanuman Ganga and Yamuna rivers.It is located at the Distance of 13kms from Yamunotri.Hanuman Chatti is nestled in the Himalayas and surrounded by the dense forests.The riverside scenic beauty at Hanuman Chatti acts as a Perfect place to experience nature and the Countryside.It is mostly frequented by the travlers because it is a popular trekking spot in the region.
    </string>
    <string name="gangotrides">
<b>Gangotri Dham</b>, located at the height of 3,100 meters on the Himalayan range in Uttarkashi district of Uttarakhand, one of the char dhams (the most sacred pilgrimage circuits in northern India with four holy destinations), Gangotri, in Uttarkashi, is a small town with the temple of Goddess Ganga at its heart. It holds a very special place in the hearts of Hindus. Amongst all the natural beauty and grace which the mountains and altitude of the place affords, what makes Gangotri one of the holiest places is its familiar connection with River Ganga (the Ganges). Gangotri offers stunning views all around.
    </string>
    <string name="kedarnath">
<b>O</b>ne of the most revered temple destinations of India, Kedarnath town is nestled in the mighty Garhwal Himalayas .It is located in the Rudraprayag district of Uttarkhand, is one of the most paramount locations for worshipers of Lord Shiva. It is an uphill trek for about 22 kilometers from Gauri kund.  A Conical rock formation inside the temple is worshipped as Lord Shiva in his “Sadashiva” form.
    </string>
    <string name="saptarishi">
•	Saptarshi kund is located at a distance of 10kms from Yamunotri.To reach the Saptarshi kund we need to go through an difficult Trek but the sight of the emerald blue lake is surrounded by frozen glaciers which is very impressive.This lake is also said to be the source of the rare lotus “Bhrama Kamal”.This glacier lake of a half kilometer long , is surrounded by the rocky glaciers and is fed by Champasar glacier.
    </string>
    <string name="janki">
        •	Janki Chatti is familiarly known for its Hot water Springs. It is situated at an elevation of 2,650 mts above sea level and it is also popular for its natural splendour.It is located at the distance of 6kms from Yamunotri which is totally surrounded by the high mountains at all sides.
    </string>
    <string name="bad_des">
        The Badrinath Temple also known as the Badrinarayan Temple, located in Uttarakhand Badrinath town. Badrinath is sacred to Lord Vishnu, particularly in Vishnu dual form of Nara-Narayana. It is one of the four Char Dhams (four important pilgrimages) in the state. Badrinath temple was re-established by “Adi Shankracharya” in the 8th century as part of his mission to brighten Hinduism. Badrinath is located at an altitude of around 3,100 m which is located in the Garhwal Himalayas, on the banks of the Alaknanda river.
    </string>
</resources>